<textcomponents> 

<component id="ID_txt01">
<text><![CDATA[Information Theft]]></text>
</component> 

<component id="ID_txt02">
<text><![CDATA[Data Loss and Manipulation]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_txt03">
<text><![CDATA[Identity Theft]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_txt04">
<text><![CDATA[Disruption of Service]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_txt05">
<text><![CDATA[<b>404<br>page not<br>found</b>]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_titleTxt01">
<text><![CDATA[<b>Information Theft</b>]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_bodyTxt01">
<text><![CDATA[Breaking into a computer to obtain confidential information. Information can be used or sold for various purposes. Example: stealing an organization's proprietary information, such as research and development information.]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_titleTxt02">
<text><![CDATA[<b>Data Loss and Manipulation</b>]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_bodyTxt02">
<text><![CDATA[Breaking into a computer to destroy or alter data records. Examples of data loss: sending a virus that reformats a computer's hard drive. Examples of data manipulation: breaking into a records system to change information, such as the price of an item.]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_titleTxt03">
<text><![CDATA[<b>Identity Theft</b>]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_bodyTxt03">
<text><![CDATA[A form of information theft where personal information is stolen for the purpose of taking over someone's identity. Using this information, an individual can obtain legal documents, apply for credit, and make unauthorized online purchases. Identity theft is a growing problem costing billions of dollars per year.]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_titleTxt04">
<text><![CDATA[<b>Disruption of Service</b>]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_bodyTxt04">
<text><![CDATA[Preventing legitimate users from accessing services to which they should be entitled.<br/>Examples: Denial of Service (DoS) attacks on servers, network devices, or network communications links]]></text>
</component>

<component id="ID_inst">
<text><![CDATA[Click the blue highlighted images for more information.]]></text>
</component>
 
</textcomponents>